MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

IPSEN PHARMA VIETNAM – HO CHI MINH

NGUYEN THANH TUAN

Phone: 0985453729

Email: tuannguyen89340518@gmail.com
Address: 7 Ward, Tan An City, Long An Province



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 07/02/1994

Nationality: Vietnamese

Gender: Male

Marital status: Single

CAREER AND DEVELOPMENT

The goal in 2018: Become a good medical representative, fulfill the assigned tasks, learn and improve career skills

The long term goal: Have enough experience to play more important role, expand the area and the field of pharmaceutical marketing.

SKILL

English: TOEIC

Computer: Proficient in Microsoft Windows Word, Excel and Power Point, advanced in SPSS, Epidata statistics

Communication and presentation skills:

Experienced in presenting and convincing, conference organizing

Independent skills: Motivated, excellent work ethics, adaptable, friendly. Have a high sense of responsibility, courageous, patient. Able to work independently as well as in a team. Interest and willingness in job developing.

EDUCATION

- 2009-2012: Long An High school for the gifted, Long An, Vietnam
- **2012-2017:** Medical pharmacist degree at Vo Truong Toan University, Can Tho. Received the excellent certificate of merit.

EXTRA ACTIVITIES

- 2008: Awarded "Young Future Leader" by the Central Committee
- **2015:** Taking part in Green Summer, Volunteer Spring in Ca Mau Province
- 2016: Taking part in charity treatment in Hau
 Giang Province
- 2017-2018: Volunteer Club "ASK ME anything, Can Tho"

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- 2016-2017: work as a Tour guide in floating market in Can Tho city, Hieutour Co., Ltd.
- 2017-2018: Lecturer at Vo Truong Toan
 University of Pharmacology-Biochemistry Clinical Pharmacology Department
- Research:

Characteristics and correlation between diabetes and proteinuria at Can Tho Hospital.

Prevalence of pharmaceutical drugs in pneumonitis treatment at Binh Tan Medical Center, Vinh Long.